{
    "id": "e84d018fc7074135854e0417b5b78bee",
    "title": "Subject and verb worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "57579735449d4163bf151358f855e34e",
            "title": "Subject Verb Worksheet",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "My brother and I …………….. cricket.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "likes"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The quality of the apples ………………. not very good.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The rise and fall of the tide ………………. due to the attraction of the moon.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The state of his affairs ………………. such as to cause anxiety to his creditors.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He or his friend …………… the secret.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "know",
                        "knows"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Time and tide ……………….. for none.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wait",
                        "waits"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Neither he nor his friend ……………… there.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Either he is mistaken or I ………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are",
                        "am"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Wool, as well as cotton, ………………. exported from India.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The leader, as well as his followers, …………….. excited.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}